A Guide to the Papers of James Washington Singleton 1770-1975
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
Papers of James Washington Singleton 1770-1975
Special Collections and University Archives, Patricia W. and J. Douglas Perry Library, Old Dominion University
MG 10
35 Hollinger Documents Cases; One Hollinger Drop-Front Print Box and One Hollinger Oversize Newspaper Box
Administrative Information
Access
The collection is open to researchers without restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Mrs. Judith Ball Wysong Cofer, January 14, 1977
Biographical/Historical Information
Biography: James W. Singleton, 1811-1892
James Washington Singleton was born on November 23, 1811 at "Paxton" in Frederick County, Virginia, the estate of his father, General James Singleton. General Singleton (1762-1815) was a Captain in the Virginia troops in 1785. He rose to the rank of Major in 1804 and commanded the Second Battalion 10th, 16th and 18th Brigades of the Virginia Militia. He commanded the 16th Brigade in the War of 1812. He served as a Justice in Frederick County from 1795-1813 and as a member of the House of Delegates during 1806 and 1807. He married Judith Throckmorton Ball in 1797 and they had seven children: James Washington, Ann, Mary, Frances, Judith, Lucy and Elizabeth. Mrs. Singleton had ancestral ties with George Washington's mother, Mary Ball of "Epping Forest", Virginia.
After attending the academy in Winchester, Virginia, James Washington Singleton moved to Kentucky in 1828. He married Mathilde Caves who died in 1832. Singleton pursued the study and practice of medicine in Kentucky. Later he married Ann Craig of Lexington, Kentucky. About 1834 he settled at Mount Sterling, Illinois. He commenced the study of law in Mount Sterling and was admitted to the Illinois bar in 1841. During these years the Singletons had a son, James Washington, Jr. but he died in infancy. Ann Craig Singleton also died about 1840.
James Washington Singleton began to distinguish himself in public service during the 1840's. In the "war" against the Mormons he was in command of a military company and he was later commissioned a brigadier-general of militia by Governor Ford of Illinois for his services in the Mormon War. He married Parthenia McDonald on April 9, 1844. He had two children by his third wife: Louise(Lily) born in 1857 and James J. Singleton born in 1860. In 1847 he was elected to represent his county in a constitutional convention. He served in the Illinois legislature representing Schuyler(Brown) County from 1850 to 1854.
The Singletons moved to Quincy where James Washington practiced law and became active in politics. He served in the state legislature from 1860 to 1862. He also represented Quincy in the state Constitutional convention of 1861. That same year he purchased the most famous country home in the area, Boscobel, a mansion set on an estate of 640 acres. Here he played the roles of gentleman farmer, lawyer, and politician. He also became deeply involved in railroad projects. He was president of two railroads: the Quincy, Alton and St. Louis and the Quincy and Toledo. He was responsible for the extension of the Wabash line through Quincy. In 1862 he served on an international commission that investigated water communication between the United States and Canada.
During the Civil War Singleton may be most accurately characterized as a Peace Democrat who maintained close ties with President Lincoln. He had met Lincoln while he was in legal practice in Illinois in the 1840's. Their friendship lasted until Lincoln's death although they held different positions on the principal political issues of the time. At the beginning of the war Singleton was offered a colonelcy in the Illinois militia by Governor Richard Yates. Although he would have commanded ten companies of cavalry, Singleton refused the commission because he did not believe in the war. He opposed Lincoln's arbitrary measures and was prominent in peace conventions at Peoria and Springfield in 1864.In November 1864 he was in Canada conferring with Clay and Tucker, Confederate "commissioners". He made several trips to Richmond late in the war. He was associated with Senator O.H. Browning of Illinois and Judge James Hughes in a scheme to buy Southern products with greenbacks move them through Grant's lines with presidential permission and sell them for a considerable profit in the North. At first Lincoln apparently approved the scheme so that federal money could pass into Southern hands. He, however, gave General Grant complete discretion in the matter. Grant withheld his approval from the operations in early 1865. Singleton apparently held informal "negotiations" with several people in Richmond including President Jefferson Davis and General Robert E. Lee. Lincoln did not give official sanction to these talks but was ready to recognize them if satisfactory Confederate proposals should emerge from the negotiations.
After the war Singleton remained active in politics and farming. Besides attending to the myriad affairs of Boscobel and raising prize stock, Singleton served two terms in the United States House of Representatives (1879-1883). In 1868 he was nominated by the Democratic convention at Monmouth, Illinois for Congress but he was defeated by Mr. John Hawley, the Republican candidate. The Democrats nominated him again in 1878, and this time he was successful. Singleton carried the city of Quincy by the unprecedented majority of 1,732 out of 3,000 votes, and received large majorities in every county in the district. He was reelected in 1880.
Singleton spent most of his later years at Boscobel.He continued to entertain lavishly, manage the affairs of his large estate and give increasing attention to railroad promotion. Political animosities did not disturb his friendships, and he was often called upon to lead civic endeavors. He did not hold any other public office although he sought unsuccessfully the position of Commissioner of Agriculture in the administration of Grover Cleveland. He moved to Baltimore to be with his daughter, Louise (Mrs. Francis W. Thomas) in the fall of 1891 and died at her home on April 4, 1892.
Scope and Content Information
The Papers of James Washington Singleton are a collection of family papers spanning the lifetime of five generations of Singleton descendants. The collection includes papers of James Singleton, the father of James W. Singleton, Lily Singleton Thomas Osburn, the daughter of James W. Singleton, the Thomas children, the grandchildren of James W. Singleton and Judith Ball Wysong Cofer, the great- granddaughter of James W. Singleton. A major portion of the collection dating from 1810 until 1940 principally concerns the lives of James Singleton, James W. Singleton and Lily Singleton Thomas Osburn.
Arrangement
The collection is divided into 11 series. They are: correspondence, legal and government documents, financial and bookkeeping records, business papers, military papers, speeches, miscellany, memorabilia, newspaper clippings, publications and photographs.
Series I: Correspondence
Subseries A: James Singleton (1762-1815)
Subseries B: Joseph Holmes Sherrard (1802-1889)
Subseries C: James Washington Singleton (1811-1892)
Subseries D: Parthenia McDonald Singleton (1824-1902)
Subseries E: Anna Singleton McDonald (1836-1929)
Subseries F: Lily Singleton Thomas Osburn (1857-1943)
Subseries G: James Jones Singleton (1860-1848)
Subseries H: Louise Singleton Thomas Kemp (1884-1969)
Subseries I: Judith Ball Thomas Wysong (1887- 1976)
Subseries J: Francis Worthington Thomas, Jr. (1889-1910)
Subseries K: Cora Elder Thomas (1894-1963)
Subseries L: Judith Ball Wysong Cofer (1923- )
Subseries M: Parthenia Marie Thomas deLoach (1892- )
Series II: Legal and government documents
Series III: Financial and bookkeeping records
Series IV: Business papers
Series V: Military papers
Series VI: Speeches
Series VII: Miscellany
Subseries A: Material of Matthew Page Andrews
Subseries B: Genealogical and Historical notes collected by Lily Singleton Thomas Osburn
Subseries C: Other Subjects
Series VIII: Memorabilia
Series IX: Newspaper clipping
Series X: Publications
Subseries A: General
Subseries B: Serial
Series XI: Photographs
Subseries A: Ambrotypes and Daguerrotypes
Subseries B: Photographic Prints
Subseries C: Prints, Sketches and Lithographs
Contents List
- Series I: Correspondence (Box Boxes 1-21)
  This series is further divided into 13 subseries. Within each subseries, the correspondence is arranged chronologically.
  - James Singleton (1762-1815)
    The correspondence of James Singleton (1762-1815) dating from 1787 to 1815. Most of the correspondence dates from the War of 1812 period and is concerned with Singleton's activities in that conflict.
    - Correspondence 1787-1801 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1804-1810 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence 1811-1813 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence March-August 1814 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence September 1814 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence October-November 1814 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence 1815 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Joseph Holmes Sherrard (1802-1889)
    The correspondence of Joseph Holmes Sherrard (1802-1889) dating from 1826 to 1911. This subseries also includes some correspondence of Sherrard's daughters, Virginia and Elizabeth Sherrard.
    - Correspondence 1826-1827 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence 1830-1838 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence 1841-1850 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence 1852-1911 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 11)
  - James Washington Singleton (1811-1892)
    The correspondence of James Washington Singleton(1811-1892) dating from 1837 to 1892. Most of the correspondence dates from the post 1860 period. There are five folders of letters from the 1860-1866 period which give a limited view of Singleton's Civil War activities. The subseries includes correspondence from the 1879 to 1883, the period when Singleton was serving in the House of Representatives. There is a good file of correspondence from the 1884-1885 period when Singleton was seeking a position in Cleveland's administration as Commissioner of Agriculture.
    - Correspondence 1837, 1839 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence 1840-1849 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence 1850-1859 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence 1860-1861 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence 1862-1863 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence 1864 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence 1865 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence 1866 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence 1867-1868 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence 1870-1872, 1874 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence 1875-1879 (Box-folder Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence 1880-1881 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1882 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence January-December 24, 1883 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence December 25-31, 1883 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence 1884 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence 1885 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence 1886-1892 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Parthenia McDonald Singleton (1824-1902)
    The correspondence of Parthenia McDonald Singleton (1824-1902) dating from 1858 to 1898. The correspondence from 1864 to 1866 includes letters from her husband, James W. during his visits to Richmond.
    - Correspondence 1858-1859 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence 1864-1866 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1880, 1883-1890 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence 1891-1892 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence 1893-1894 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence 1895-1896 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence 1896-1898 (Box-folder Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Anna Singleton McDonald (1836-1929)
    The correspondence of Anna Singleton McDonald (1836-1929) dating from 1858 to 1923.
    - Correspondence 1856-1866 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1871-1910 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence 1910-1923 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Lily Singleton Thomas Osburn (1857-1943)
    The correspondence of Lily Singleton Thomas Osburn (1857-1943) dating from 1875 to 1942. The principal correspondents in this subseries are Lily's daughter Cora and historian Matthew Page Andrews. The Andrews' correspondence (1926-1942) contains biographical information about James W. Singleton. Lily corresponded with many relatives and these letters are a good source of genealogical information.
    - Correspondence 1875-1878 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence 1880-1881 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence 1882-December 14, 1883 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence December 15-22, 1883 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence December 24-28, 1883 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence December 27-31, 1883 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence January-October, 1884 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence November-December 1884 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence 1885-1886 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence 1887 (Box-folder Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence 1888 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1889 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence 1890-1891 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence January-April 4, 1892 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence April 5, 1892 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence April 9-30, 1892 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence May-December 1892 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence 1893 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence January-September 1894 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence September-December 1894 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence January-June 1895 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence July-December 1895 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence January-May 1896 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence June-December 1896 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence January-February 24, 1897 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence February 25, 1897 (Box-folder Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence February 26, 1897 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence February 27, 1897 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence February 28, 1897 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence March 1-3, 1897 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence March 4-5, 1897 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence March 6-7, 1897 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence March 8-13, 1897 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence March 14-20, 1897 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence March 21-31, 1897 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence April, 1897 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence May-October, 1897 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence November-December, 1897 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence January-March, 1898 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence April-June, 1898 (Box-folder Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence July-December, 1898 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence January-April, 1899 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence May-December, 1899 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence January-April, 1900 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence May-July, 1900 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence August-December, 1900 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence January-August, 1901 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence September-December, 1901 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence January-February, 1902 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence March 1-4, 1902 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence March 5-6, 1902 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence March 7-8, 1902 (Box-folder Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence March 9-12, 1902 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence March 13-17, 1902 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence March 18-31, 1902 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence April-July, 1902 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence September-December, 1902 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence January-March, 1903 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence April-July, 1903 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence September-December, 1903 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence 1904 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence January-August, 1905 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence September-December, 1905 (Box-folder Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence January-February, 1906 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence March-May, 1906 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence June-July, 1906 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence August-October 15, 1906 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence October 17-November 19, 1906 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence November 11-21, 1906 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence November 23-December, 1906 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence January-June, 1907 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence August-October, 1907 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence November-December, 1907 (Box-folder Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence January-May, 1908 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence June-October, 1908 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence November-December, 1908 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence January-July, 1909 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence August-December, 1909 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence January, 1910 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence February-March, 1910 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence April-August, 1910 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence October 1-22, 1910 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence October 23, 1910 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence October 24, 1910 (Box-folder Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence October 25, 1910 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence October 26, 1910 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence October 27, 1910 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence October 28-29, 1910 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence October 30-31, 1910 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence November 1-3, 1910 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence November 4-10, 1910 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence November 11-28, 1910 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence December, 1910 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence January, 1911 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence February-July, 1911 (Box-folder Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence August-September, 1911 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence November-December, 1911 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence January-February, 1912 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence March-May, 1912 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence June-December, 1912 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence 1913 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence 1914 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence January-June, 1915 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence August-December, 1915 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence 1916 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence January-August, 1917 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence September, 1917 (Box-folder Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence 1918 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence May-October, 1919 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence November 1-22, 1919 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence November 23-25, 1919 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence November 26-30, 1919 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence December, 1919 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence January-February, 1920 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence March-April, 1920 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence May-July, 1920 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence August-September, 1920 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence October-December, 1920 (Box-folder Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence January-February, 1921 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence March-June, 1921 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence July-September, 1921 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence October-November, 1921 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence December, 1921 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence January-April, 1922 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence May-August, 1922 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence October-November, 1922 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence December, 1922 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence January-April, 1923 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence May, 1923 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence June-July, 1923 (Box-folder Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence August-September, 1923 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence October-November, 1923 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence December, 1923 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence January, 1924 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence February-March, 1924 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence May-June, 1924 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence July-September, 1924 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence October-December, 1924 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence January, 1925 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence February, 1925 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence March, 1925 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence April-May, 1925 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence June-July, 1925 (Box-folder Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence August-December, 1925 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence January, 1926 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence February-April, 1926 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence May-June, 1926 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence July-August, 1926 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence September, 1926 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence October-November, 1926 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence December, 1926 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence January, 1927 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence February-March, 1927 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence April-June, 1927 (Box-folder Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence July-October, 1927 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence November-December, 1927 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence January-February, 1928 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence March, 1928 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence April-May, 1928 (Box-folder Box 16, Folder 5)